<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<messages>
	<message name="message1">
		<pic>Russell</pic>
		<character><![CDATA[Russell]]></character>
		<job><![CDATA[]]></job>
		<title><![CDATA[Email warrant]]></title>
		<text><![CDATA[The sender of the threatening emails claims that our victim turned his or her daughter into a drug addict? That could be a strong motive.

I'll try to find out who the email sender is and ask for a warrant.]]></text>
	</message>
	<message name="message2">
		<pic>Russell</pic>
		<character><![CDATA[Russell]]></character>
		<job><![CDATA[]]></job>
		<title><![CDATA[Warrant granted]]></title>
		<text><![CDATA[The sender of the threatening emails is Terry McCoy. The warrant to search his place was granted, so make sure you pay him a visit. 
		
Also, you should go back to the crime scene. Maybe you can find some more information about McCoy's daughter and the subpoena.]]></text>
	</message>
	<message name="message3">
		<pic>Russell</pic>
		<character><![CDATA[Russell]]></character>
		<job><![CDATA[]]></job>
		<title><![CDATA[Security access log]]></title>
		<text><![CDATA[The security access log from the clinic has arrived. It's waiting for you on the lab computer. 
		
Also, I've asked Greg to pull up Melissa McCoy's tox screen. Ask him to show it to you when you're back here.]]></text>
	</message>
	<message name="message4">
		<pic>Russell</pic>
		<character><![CDATA[Russell]]></character>
		<job><![CDATA[]]></job>
		<title><![CDATA[Assistant involved?]]></title>
		<text><![CDATA[I wonder what Anna Steward was doing at the crime scene so late that evening.

Go and visit her while I'll be working on a warrant. I'll send her address to your locations.]]></text>
	</message>
	<message name="message5">
		<pic>Russell</pic>
		<character><![CDATA[Russell]]></character>
		<job><![CDATA[]]></job>
		<title><![CDATA[Bank account]]></title>
		<text><![CDATA[I'm glad Anna Steward at least provided a DNA sample.

In the meantime, I have been working on a warrant to look into the clinic's bank account. I get the feeling that money was involved in this case. Make sure you look into it on the lab computer when you're back.]]></text>
	</message>
	<message name="message6">
		<pic>Russell</pic>
		<character><![CDATA[Russell]]></character>
		<job><![CDATA[]]></job>
		<title><![CDATA[Pharmacist warrant]]></title>
		<text><![CDATA[This pharmacist becomes more and more suspicious. Thankfully, the judge agrees and has issued a warrant to search the pharmacy and to get a DNA sample.

Go and see what he has to hide.]]></text>
	</message>
	<message name="message7">
		<pic>Russell</pic>
		<character><![CDATA[Russell]]></character>
		<job><![CDATA[]]></job>
		<title><![CDATA[Tying up loose ends]]></title>
		<text><![CDATA[You've gathered enough evidence to wrap up the case.

Click the attachment to file your report. Russell]]></text>
	</message>
</messages>
