<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<activity name="GA_BloodStain">
	<screen name="screen1">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[First we need to extract the DNA from the bloodstain samples.

Open both containers and take out the swabs, then use the scissors to cut both of them.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen2">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Great. I’ve labeled two tubes filled with lysis buffer with F for “floor” and W for “wall”.

Use the tweezers to transfer the swabs to the corresponding tubes.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen3">	
		<instruct><![CDATA[The lysis buffer breaks the blood cells apart and sets the DNA free.

That takes about 30 minutes.]]></instruct>
		<caption num="1"><![CDATA[DNA]]></caption>
		<caption num="2"><![CDATA[Blood cell]]></caption>
		<caption num="3"><![CDATA[Cell particle]]></caption>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen4">	
		<instruct><![CDATA[Next, transfer the swabs over to the empty tubes.

We’ll keep them just in case something goes wrong with the analysis.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen5">	
		<instruct><![CDATA[Now place both samples in the centrifuge to separate the DNA in the fluid from the broken cell material.]]></instruct>		
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen6">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[As the sample is centrifuged, the broken-up cell particles move to the bottom of the tube and form a pellet, while the DNA stays in the supernatant, the fluid above the pellet.]]></instruct>
		<caption num="1"><![CDATA[DNA]]></caption>
		<caption num="2"><![CDATA[Cell particle]]></caption>
		<caption num="3"><![CDATA[Pellet]]></caption>
		<caption num="4"><![CDATA[Supernatant]]></caption>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen7">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[That’ll do. Place the tubes back in the tray.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen8">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[To clean the DNA, we’ll use special filters.
		
Use the pipette to transfer the supernatant, which contains the DNA, from both of your original tubes to the new tubes on the left.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen9">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Next, place the samples in the centrifuge and start the machine.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen10">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[The fluid containing the DNA is forced through the filter due to the centrifugal force, but only the DNA molecules stick to the filter material.]]></instruct>
		<caption num="1"><![CDATA[DNA]]></caption>
		<caption num="2"><![CDATA[Filter]]></caption>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen11">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Take out the samples and place them in the tray.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen12">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Next, take the filters from both of the tubes you’ve just centrifuged and place them in the corresponding empty tubes on the right.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen13">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[The last step of the extraction process is to remove the cleaned DNA from the filters with fresh eluting buffer.

Use the pipette to transfer a specific amount of eluting buffer to both samples.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen14">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[The eluting buffer removes the DNA from the filter.]]></instruct>
		<caption num="1"><![CDATA[DNA]]></caption>
		<caption num="2"><![CDATA[Filter]]></caption>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen15">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Great. Put the empty filters in the tubes on the left. We’ll store them just in case.]]></instruct>
		<label name="floor"><![CDATA[DNA filter F]]></label>
		<label name="wall"><![CDATA[DNA filter W]]></label>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen16">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Now that the DNA is extracted from the blood cells, you’re ready to amplify the DNA. We’re going to do a PCR, Polymerase Chain Reaction.

First, transfer a specific amount of the replicating solution to both samples.]]></instruct>
		<label name="replicating"><![CDATA[Replicating solution]]></label>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen17">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[The polymerase enzyme in the replicating solution will make thousands of copies of the DNA in our sample.

To start this 2-hour process, transfer the samples to the PCR machine and press start.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen18">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Since we don’t want to copy all of the DNA, the PCR is set up so that it only copies 13 specific DNA markers.

DNA markers, also called Short Tandem Repeats (STR), are regions on the DNA that are unique in every person.]]></instruct>
		<caption num="1"><![CDATA[DNA]]></caption>
		<caption num="2"><![CDATA[Marker]]></caption>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen19">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[The amplification is done. Place the samples back in the tray.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen20">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Next, we need to separate and sort the DNA markers. The genetic analyzer is going to take care of that.

Place our samples in the genetic analyzer.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen21">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Good. Now start the machine.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen22">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[In the genetic analyzer, the DNA markers are pushed through a small gel-filled tube. Small markers move through the gel faster than large markers.

A sensor then records the time the markers exit the tube.]]></instruct>
		<caption num="1"><![CDATA[Gel-filled tube]]></caption>
		<caption num="2"><![CDATA[DNA marker]]></caption>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen23">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[The results are in. Click on the computer to access them.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen24">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Here is your first DNA profile, also called DNA fingerprint, from the blood you collected from the wall.

Click on the first marker to zoom in.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen25">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[This marker is represented by two different peaks, because this person has inherited two different copies of this marker – one from the mother, one from the father.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen26">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[The number below each peak indicates how often this particular copy is present in the person’s DNA.

Click the marker to zoom out.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen27">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Click on another marker to zoom in.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen28">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[This marker has only one peak, because the two copies the person inherited from mother and father are the same.

Click on the marker again to zoom out.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="screen29">		
		<instruct><![CDATA[Since each person has a different set AND different numbers of DNA markers, no two people have the same DNA profile.]]></instruct>
	</screen>
	<screen name="comparison">		
		<instruct num="1"><![CDATA[Drag the DNA profile from the wall bloodstains to the left viewing area.]]></instruct>	
		<instruct num="2"><![CDATA[Drag the DNA profile from the floor bloodstains to the right viewing area.]]></instruct>		
		<instruct num="3"><![CDATA[Do these DNA profiles match?]]></instruct>	
		<wrongText><![CDATA[The DNA profiles are identical.]]></wrongText>	
		<codisTitle><![CDATA[CODIS]]></codisTitle>
		<codisText><![CDATA[The Combined DNA Index Systems (CODIS) is a database of over 4 million DNA profiles. The profiles come from convicted felons, evidence, and missing persons.]]></codisText>		
	</screen>
	<label name="wall"><![CDATA[Bloodstains on wall]]></label>
	<label name="floor"><![CDATA[Bloodstains on floor]]></label>
	<label name="lysis"><![CDATA[Lysis buffer]]></label>
	<label name="f"><![CDATA[F]]></label>
	<label name="w"><![CDATA[W]]></label>
	<label name="filter"><![CDATA[Tubes with filter]]></label>
	<label name="eluting"><![CDATA[Eluting buffer]]></label>
	<markerPrefix><![CDATA[Marker # ]]></markerPrefix>
	<markerHeading num="1" name="wall"><![CDATA[DNA PROFILE - BLOODSTAINS ON WALL]]></markerHeading>
	<markerHeading num="2" name="floor"><![CDATA[DNA PROFILE - BLOODSTAINS ON FLOOR]]></markerHeading>
	<markerHeading num="3" name="stains"><![CDATA[DNA PROFILE - BLOODSTAINS]]></markerHeading>
	<markerHeading num="4" name="victim"><![CDATA[VICTIM'S DNA PROFILE]]></markerHeading>
	<markerHeading num="5" name="swab1"><![CDATA[DNA PROFILE #1 - FINGERNAIL SWABS]]></markerHeading>
	<markerHeading num="6" name="swab2"><![CDATA[DNA PROFILE #2 - FINGERNAIL SWABS]]></markerHeading>
	<profile num="1" name="wall"><![CDATA[Bloodstains on the wall]]></profile>
	<profile num="2" name="floor"><![CDATA[Bloodstains on the floor]]></profile>
	<profile num="3" name="stains"><![CDATA[Bloodstains]]></profile>
	<profile num="4" name="victim"><![CDATA[Victim]]></profile>
	<profile num="5" name="swab1"><![CDATA[Fingernail swabs #1]]></profile>
	<profile num="5" name="swab2"><![CDATA[Fingernail swabs #2]]></profile>
	<profileUNK><![CDATA[Unknown DNA Profiles]]></profileUNK>
	<profileREF><![CDATA[Reference DNA Profiles]]></profileREF>
	<continueBtn><![CDATA[Continue]]></continueBtn>
	<matchBtn><![CDATA[MATCH]]></matchBtn>
	<noMatchBtn><![CDATA[NO MATCH]]></noMatchBtn>
	<okBtn><![CDATA[Okay.]]></okBtn>
	<searchBtn><![CDATA[SEARCH CODIS]]></searchBtn>
</activity>